At Quan The Am Pagoda in Da Nang, multicolored clouds
Chùa Quán Thế Âm, Đà Nẵng, mây ngũ sắc
appeared in the sky on the day of veneration of
hiện giữa trời đúng ngày chiêm bái xá
Buddha's relics.  On the morning of May 31, 2025,
lợi Phật. Sáng ngày 31 tháng năm 2025
at Quan The Am Pagoda in Da Nang, as
tại chùa Quán Thế Âm, Đà Nẵng, khi hàng
thousands of people were respectfully venerating the
ngàn người đang thành kính chiêm bái Xá
Buddha's relics, a dazzling array of five colors appeared
Lợi Phật, mời ngũ sắc rực rỡ hiện ra
against the blue sky.  This is not the
giữa trời xanh. Đây không phải là lần
first time miraculous phenomena have
đầu tiên những hiện tượng nhiệm màu xuất
appeared in the sky over places of veneration for the
hiện trên bầu trời tại các nơi tôn Chí
Buddha's relics.  At Thanh Tam Pagoda, Ba Den Mountain
Xá Lợi Phật. Tại chùa Thanh Tâm, núi Bà
, Quan Su Pagoda, Tam Truc Pagoda, and Yen Tu, there have
Đen, chùa Quán Sứ, chùa Tam Trúc, Yên Tử
also been miraculous
cũng từng hiện ra những dấu ấn kỳ diệu
natural landmarks that have moved many people
giữa thiên nhiên khiến nhiều người không
.  The Buddha taught that
khỏi xúc động. Đức Phật đã chỉ dạy rằng
he is the teacher of both humans and celestial beings.  This
Đức Phật là thầy của nhân thiên. Đây có
is perhaps a joy for
lẽ là niềm vui của những người con Phật
Vietnamese Buddhists in particular, as well as Buddhists
Việt Nam nói riêng cũng như Phật tử trên
worldwide, as it has resonated with heaven and earth, and with the
toàn thế giới đã cảm ứng tới trời đất,
celestial beings.  Therefore, the celestial beings
cảm ứng tới chư thiên. Cho nên chư thiên
also rejoiced and offered veneration to the
cũng hoan hỉ để cúng dường kim thân xá
sacred relics of the Buddha.  These miraculous events
lợi của Đức Thế Tôn. Những điều vi diệu
are living proof of the
ấy là minh chứng sống động cho sự linh
sacredness of Buddhism and especially of the
thiêng của Phật giáo và đặc biệt là cho
miraculous power of the Buddha's relics.  If you have
sự mỏ nhiệm của Xá Lợi Phật. Nếu có
the opportunity, sincerely visit and venerate the
duyên, hãy thành tâm đến chiêm Bái Xá
Buddha's relics to strengthen your faith and receive
Lợi Phật để tăng trưởng niềm tin và được
many blessings and benefits.
nhiều lợi ích phước báu.